What are you doing?
I'm making leaf fish.
You're good.
This is a fish and this is an octopus!
It isn't a starfish?
I'm sorry...
Starfish Palace of Books
Rin, I have something for you.
A book about fish!
Fish Encyclopaedia
This is a salmon!
It's the one that's slightly salted!
Does she want to eat it?
Rin. Look, this is a flounder.
A flounder?
It has both eyes on the same side.
Ah, it's true!
Next, this one!
It looks like a pufferfish.
I see it, I see it.
Daikichi, look!
You can't cheat.
Why is this cheating?
Cutting is cheating.
This isn't cheating. It's called "adults' wisdom."
What should I do?
It got all chewed up!
There are holes in this acorn!
Holes?
Maybe it was an insect?
That also happened to ours.
Reina even got mad when I said she couldn't bring those acorns home anymore.
So what should I do?
The insects will get out of the acorn and eat the leaves.
With the leaves? We pressed them.
Pressed leaves?
I'm home!
Rin, wash your hands first!
Just a moment!
Daikichi, I'm leaving!
Leaves Aquarium